[
  {
    "question": "In which part of your body would you find the cruciate ligament?",
    "take": "A => Knee\nB => Elbow\nC => Shoulder\nD => Ankle",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of the main antagonist in the Shakespeare play Othello?",
    "take": "A => Iago\nB => Cassio\nC => Roderigo\nD => Brabantio",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "question": "What element is denoted by the chemical symbol Sn in the periodic table?",
    "take": "A => Tin\nB => Silver\nC => Titanium\nD => Silicon",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many of Henry VIII's wives were called Catherine?",
    "take": "A => 1\nB => 2\nC => 3\nD => 4",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "question": "What was the most popular girls name in the UK in 2021?",
    "take": "A => Olivia\nB => Amelia\nC => Isla\nD => Ava",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of the 1976 film about the Watergate scandal, starring Robert Redford and Dustin Hoffman?",
    "take": "A => Nixon\nB => The Post\nC => Frost/Nixon\nD => All the President's Men",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which comedian was the second permanent host of Never Mind the Buzzcocks after Mark Lamarr?",
    "take": "A => Rhod Gilbert\nB => Simon Amstell\nC => Noel Fielding\nD => Bill Bailey",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which popular video game franchise has released games with the subtitles World At War and Black Ops?",
    "take": "A => Call of Duty\nB => Battlefield\nC => Medal of Honor\nD => Halo",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "question": "In what US State is the city Nashville?",
    "take": "A => Alabama\nB => Kentucky\nC => Tennessee\nD => Georgia",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which rock band was founded by Fred Mercury in 1970?",
    "take": "A => The Who\nB => The Rolling Stones\nC => The Beatles\nD => Queen",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the currency of Denmark?",
    "take": "A => Euro\nB => Krone\nC => Pound\nD => Dollar",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which Tennis Grand Slam is played on a clay surface?",
    "take": "A => French Open\nB => Wimbledon\nC => US Open\nD => Australian Open",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "question": "In which European country would you find the Rijksmuseum?",
    "take": "A => France\nB => Germany\nC => Netherlands\nD => Spain",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many films have Al Pacino and Robert De Niro appeared in together?",
    "take": "A => 4\nB => 3\nC => 2\nD => 1",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "question": "What was the old name for a Snickers bar before it changed in 1990?",
    "take": "A => Boost\nB => Twix\nC => Marathon\nD => Milky Way",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who was the head of state in Japan during the second world war?",
    "take": "A => Emperor Meiji\nB => Emperor Akihito\nC => Emperor Hirohito\nD => Emperor Taisho",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the smallest planet in our solar system?",
    "take": "A => Mercury\nB => Mars\nC => Venus\nD => Earth",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who wrote the novels Gone Girl and Sharp Objects?",
    "take": "A => Ruth Ware\nB => Paula Hawkins\nC => Liane Moriarty\nD => Gillian Flynn",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which legendary surrealist artist is famous for painting melting clocks?",
    "take": "A => Salvador Dali\nB => Pablo Picasso\nC => Rene Magritte\nD => Joan Miro",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which football club plays its home games at Loftus Road?",
    "take": "A => Fulham\nB => Queens Park Rangers\nC => Chelsea\nD => Arsenal",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "question": "Continental United States has 4 time zones, can you name them?",
    "take": "A => Alaska, Georgia, Ohaio, Florida\nB => Virginia, LA, New Yourk, San Fransico\nC => Decota, Montania, Alabama, Texas\nD => Pacific, Mountain, Central, Eastern",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "question": "What was the Turkish city of Istanbul called before 1930?",
    "take": "A => Constantinople\nB => Smyrna\nC => Byzantium\nD => Troy",
    "answer": "Constantinople"
  },
  {
    "question": "From which US city do the band The Killers originate?",
    "take": "A => Las Vegas\nB => Los Angeles\nC => New York\nD => San Francisco",
    "answer": "Las Vegas"
  },
  {
    "question": "Name the Coffee shop in US sitcom Friends.",
    "take": "A => Star Bucks\nB => McDonald\nC => Central Park\nD => 16bins Coffee and Tea",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many human players are there on each side in a polo match?",
    "take": "A => 4\nB => 3\nC => 2\nD => 1",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "question": "In what year did Tony Blair become British Prime Minister?",
    "take": "A => 1997\nB => 1998\nC => 1999\nD => 2000",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many times has England won the men's football World Cup?",
    "take": "A => 1\nB => 2\nC => 3\nD => 4",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the capital of New Zealand?",
    "take": "A => Christchurch\nB => Auckland\nC => Wellington\nD => Hamilton",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "question": "Street artist Banksy is originally associated with which British city?",
    "take": "A => London\nB => Bristol\nC => Manchester\nD => Birmingham",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "question": "From what grain is the Japanese spirit Sake made?",
    "take": "A => Rice\nB => Wheat\nC => Barley\nD => Rye",
    "answer": "A"
  }
]